findyourdegree.com 2014-10-20

# Privacy Policy - Earn an Online Degree - Online College Search from Top Online Universities - FindYourDegree.com

## Privacy Policy and User Agreement for FindYourDegree.com

## Effective Date: 11/19/2012

This privacy policy applies to AchieveYourCareer.com owned and operated by mediaspike. FindYourDegree.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Your privacy is very important to us and you can rest assured that our privacy practices conform to the highest industry standards. mediaspike (FindYourDegree.com) created this statement in order to assure you that any and all information that we gather about you supports our efforts in providing you with the most fulfilling learning services available. We have taken the proper measures to ensure that your experience with us is safe and secure. Collecting your personally identifiable information also allows us to provide services and features that will most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easy and pleasant.

We will never sell your information to other companies except as described in this policy. Your privacy is important to us and we do everything possible to protect it. This statement details our information gathering and sharing practices for FindYourDegree.com.

mediaspike (ÒFindYourDegree.comÓ) has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally identifiable information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.findyourdegree.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@FindYourDegree.com](mailto:info@FindYourDegree.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

## Information We Collect and How We Use It

When you request school information through us, we will need to collect your name, e-mail address, in some instances age, and mailing address. This information allows us, or the school, to process your information request and contact you if necessary. You will receive communications via email from our school partners you specifically request information from. Additionally, if you choose to participate in a contest or a promotion, we may ask for your name, address and phone number in order to administer the contest and notify the winners.

If you volunteer to participate in an online survey, we may ask for contact information and possibly additional information such as your interests and demographics. Supplying this information is strictly voluntary. The information is used to provide you with a more personalized learning experience.

## Communications From the Site

We do not send promotional emails from this site.

## Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

Information Disclosure

When you request more information from a school partner, we share your information with that partner in order to fulfill your request. We do not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information with anyone outside of FindYourDegree.com other than with the specific school partner you requested information from or as described in this privacy policy.

We may provide your information as required by law or legal process; to protect and defend the rights of FindYourDegree.com, the FindYourDegree.com site or the users and, under circumstances we believe reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety of users of FindYourDegree.com, this site or the public.

We supplement the information that you provide to us by using a third party verification service to verify contact information for our leads to our school partners. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing.

If you use our blog on FindYourDegree.com, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog contact us at [info@FindYourDegree.com](mailto:info@FindYourDegree.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

If you submit a testimonial, we receive permission to post testimonials that include personally identifiable information prior to posting. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [info@FindYourDegree.com](mailto:info@FindYourDegree.com).

## Business Transitions

In the event FindYourDegree.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information.

## Links to External Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by www.FindYourDegree.com. Please be aware that we, FindYourDegree.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

## Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track usersÕ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to pre-populate the forms and improve the users experience on the site.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a userÕs computer for record-keeping purposes. We do use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site .We link our cookies to your personally identifiable information so that you may visit, search, and sign-up on our site and return several days later without having to reenter the information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Browsers usually provide the option to disable this feature. We use cookies in the event it creates a better user experience. We use a third-party service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate to track usage and volume statistics. We have no access or control of these third party cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Access

If your personally information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete by logging onto the site and re-populate the form to modify your information and resubmit your request.

Should you want to modify or delete information previously provided, please email [info@FindYourDegree.com](mailto:info@FindYourDegree.com).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Security

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All information is stored on a secure server that is not accessible through the Internet.

Your profile and information are contained on an independent third-party secure database server. To protect the security of your personally identifiable information, FindYourDegree.com limits access to user data to authorized FindYourDegree.com employees. We will not disclose any personally identifiable information except as described in this policy and in its User Agreement. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary.

## Children's Guidelines

At FindYourDegree.com, a child's safety is very important to us. We are committed to protecting the online privacy of children. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personally identifiable information about children under the age of 13.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

By using our Web site and requesting information through from our school partners, you consent to the collection and use of this information by FindYourDegree.com.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a prominent notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

Contact Information for Questions Relating to Privacy Inquiries regarding this privacy statement, or regarding any other aspects of FindYourDegree.com or its web site, should be sent via email to: [info@FindYourDegree.com](mailto:info@FindYourDegree.com).

Inquiries can also be sent via U.S. mail to:

Privacy Department c/o FindYourDegree.com: 29 Harvard St, Brookline, MA 02445
